prosoccer.gr 2016-05-28

# ProSoccer - Privacy Policy

The **Pro** gnosis **Soccer** team that manages ProSoccer.GR, values its visitors privacy, by implementing a safe and friendly web user experience. Since 2002 we have offered our free soccer predictions without requiring, collecting or maintaining any sensitive personal information of our visitors. We provide this page to explain what types of data is collected when you visit us and how it is used. 

## Anonymous Data Usage

Like most standard websites, we collect anonymous data which are stored in our server's log files. Furthermore we use the Google Analytics service which also collects anonymous data (described below). All of these are used only by us, for the sole purpose of maintaining the site operation. Through them we monitor the availability of our site, measure its performance and identify possible problems in order to improve our users experience. 

### Log Files

The basic information collected in the web server log files include your Internet Protocol address (IP address) and the timestamp of your visit. Extended logs may also include the total time of your visit, your ISP (internet service provider), the type and version of browser you used, platform type, which pages you have viewed, referring or exit pages and number of clicks. The are not linked to personally identifiable information. We safeguard all information stored in log files with the best and up to date information security practices. 

### Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics tool provided by Google Inc. (“Google”), which collects anonymous data to track and examine the use of our site, prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network according to [Google's privacy policy found here.](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You can also read [how Google uses data](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) when you visit our website. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

[Web cookies](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) (also known as HTTP cookies, or just cookies) are parcels of text that are sent by a server to a Web browser, and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. In other words, a cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s computer that is tied to information about the user. 

[Web beacons](http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/W/Web_beacon.html) are objects that are embedded in a webpage or email that are invisible to the user, but allow checking that a user has viewed the page or email. Other names are web bug, tracking bug, tag or page tag. 

_We do not use cookies to store information_ like your personal preferences for our site's user interface. However some third party business partners (for example, advertisers) may use cookies and web beacons to implement advertisements on or site (described below). This site has no access to, or control of advertisers' web cookies or web beacons. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. Please check your browser's help section for instructions on how to do this. 

**In the future any use of cookies by our site will include showing you a popup during your visit, asking you once to consent on the use of them.**

## Advertising

Our free content site is supported by third party advertisements. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as web cookies and web beacons. These may transmit to advertisers information including your IP address, the browser you used to visit our site, platform used and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. 

### Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

This website uses Google AdSense, a service that enables the integration of advertisements provided by Google Inc. (“Google”), which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). The use of DART cookies enables the serving of adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”) or may be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. **It does NOT track personal information about you** , such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. 

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>. Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies. Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies. 

ProSoccer.GR has no access or control over these cookies. By using our website, you agree to the processing of the information obtained from you by Google in the manner and for the purpose described above. 

## Privacy of E-Mail Communications

Feel free to [contact us](mailto://contact_us@prosoccer.gr) through private e-mails, as we will never publish your name, contact info, email address, nor share then with third party partners.
